<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Posts on Nailed It</title>
    <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Posts on Nailed It</description>
    <generator>Hugo</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 11:30:03 -0400</lastBuildDate>
    <atom:link href="http://localhost:1313/posts/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>What is Nailed.It?</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/zeiher-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 23 Oct 2025 11:30:03 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/zeiher-post/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;If you are in the construction field looking for a job, this app is for you! This app is designed to help connect construction workers with companies that are looking to hire, in a simple and easy way. Companies can create profiles and post what kind of workers they need, including skills, experience, and job location. Workers can also create profiles that show their trade, certifications, and availability. The app then shows users potential matches based on what they’re looking for, allowing both workers and companies to show interest in each other. When both sides are interested, they can connect and communicate directly through the app, making the hiring process faster and easier for everyone involved.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Brian Smith</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/shanklin-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 16 Oct 2025 11:29:14 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/shanklin-post/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;Nailed.it has been a game-changer for our company. For years, finding reliable workers on short notice was one of our biggest challenges, especially during peak project seasons. Since we started using Nailed.it, we’ve been able to connect with skilled laborers faster and more efficiently than ever.&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>⭐️⭐️⭐️⭐️⭐️ “Super easy way to find construction jobs!&#34;</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/hofer/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 12:15:37 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/hofer/</guid>
      <description>&lt;p&gt;This app is like Tinder for construction work, and I love it. I just set up my profile, swipe through jobs, and match with contractors instantly. The pay is shown upfront, the matches actually fit my skills, and I’ve been able to find steady work way faster than before. Highly recommend!&lt;/p&gt;</description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Larson Post</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/larson-post/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 12:12:53 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/larson-post/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Zeiher Page</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/zeiher-page/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 14 Oct 2025 12:10:40 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/zeiher-page/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
    <item>
      <title>Testpost</title>
      <link>http://localhost:1313/posts/testpost/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 11 Oct 2025 19:41:01 -0400</pubDate>
      <guid>http://localhost:1313/posts/testpost/</guid>
      <description></description>
    </item>
  </channel>
</rss>
